CS-700 Assignment 2

This assignment contains 2 programs one to calculate the execution time for sorting an array and the other one to do white box testing for sine and cosine values. The program contains the following:

1. Main file containing both modules.
	a. Summary - . Running the main() function will run both the modules. Both modules will run consecutively. 
	b. It contains the following file :
		i. main.cpp

2. Module 1 - Execution time for sorting random, sorted and reversed arrays.
	a. Summary - Running this program to calculate the execution time for sorting random, sorted and reversed arrays.
	b. It contains the following files :
		i. arraySorting.cpp
		ii. arraySorting.h

3. Module 2 - White box testing of sines and cosines.
	a. Summary - Running this program will test sine/cosine functions with different values using whitebox testing.
	b. It contains the following files :
		i. sin_cos.cpp
		ii. sin_cos.h

Github Repo Link -> https://github.com/syedfaisaljaved/cs700_Assignment2
